<?xml version="1.0"?><quiz>	<title>Challenge Questions: Research Misconduct</title>	<module>			<title>Challenge Questions: Responsible Authorship and Peer Review</title>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>				Which of the following are examples of research misconduct?				</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">					Altering research data.					</answer>					<answer value="b">					Using other people's written words or ideas without attribution.					</answer>					<answer value="c">					Sexual harassment of colleagues.					</answer>					<answer value="d">					Cruelty to research animals.					</answer>					<answer value="e">					All of the above.					</answer>					<answer value="f">					Two of the above.					</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>				Why did the Office of Science and Technology Policy develop a policy for and a definition of research misconduct in 2000?				</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">					The rising number of misconduct cases necessitated government action.					</answer>					<answer value="b">					There was a lack of uniformity across federal agencies about policies and the definition of misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="c">					There was a need to further protect the people who reported misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="d">					There was a need to further protect the people who are subjects of misconduct allegations.					</answer>					<answer value="e">					All of the above.					</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>				Which of the following are not addressed by the Office of Science and Technology Policy's definition of misconduct?				</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">					Institutional responsibility in reporting misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="b">					The definition of fabrication, falsification, and plagiarism.					</answer>					<answer value="c">					Providing whistle-blowers with compensation for reporting an allegation that turns out to be misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="d">					Protecting the rights of whistle-blowers and subjects of misconduct allegations.					</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>				Which of the following is true?				</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">					Researchers at academic institutions are legally obligated to report misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="b">					Institutions must have policies in place for the inquiry, investigation, and adjudication of allegations of misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="c">					The federal government has to be immediately contacted in every case of alleged misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="d">					Researchers found guilty of misconduct can never work as scientists again.					</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>				What is the False Claims Act?				</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">					Legislation dating from the Civil War which protects the government from fraudulent contractors.					</answer>					<answer value="b">					Legislation that grants people who report misconduct 15% to 30% of the resulting settlement in the case of misconduct.					</answer>					<answer value="c">					Legislation that protects people who report misconduct if it can be shown that the whistle-blower suffered a discriminatory action as retaliation for the allegation.					</answer>					<answer value="d">					None of the above.					</answer>					<answer value="e">					All of the above.					</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>				Which of the following is probably not the most appropriate first step if someone suspects misconduct?				</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">					Talking to the person who is believed to be implicated.					</answer>					<answer value="b">					Talking to a peer or a department chair about the event.					</answer>					<answer value="c">					Talking to the ombudsperson at the institution.					</answer>					<answer value="d">					Reporting the event to the inspector general at the federal agency that oversees the research.					</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>	</module></quiz>