<?xml version="1.0"?><quiz>	<title>Challenge Questions: Responsible Authorship and Peer Review</title>	<module>			<title>Challenge Questions: Responsible Authorship and Peer Review</title>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>Which of the following activities should enable someone to be included as an author on a paper?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">The individual was involved in the conception and design of the experiments that led to the article.</answer>					<answer value="b">The individual performed data collection for the experiments.</answer>					<answer value="c">The individual donated laboratory space for the experiments.</answer>					<answer value="d">The individual was involved in the drafting, revision, and final approval of the article.</answer>					<answer value="e">All of the above.</answer>					<answer value="f">Two of the above.</answer>					<!--<answer value="f" correct="correct">All of the above.</answer>-->								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>Should the same data be reported in more than one published article?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">Never.</answer>					<answer value="b">Under certain circumstances.</answer>					<answer value="c">Only with the approval of a journal editor.</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>At what point should the subject of authorship come up during a research project?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">When the paper is being drafted.</answer>					<answer value="b">When someone is asked to participate in a research project.</answer>					<answer value="c">When someone joins a laboratory.</answer>					<answer value="d">It is not necessary to discuss authorship, since parties usually act responsibly.</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>Who is responsible if there is fraud or plagiarism in a published research paper with multiple authors?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">The first author.</answer>					<answer value="b">The last author.</answer>					<answer value="c">The journal editor.</answer>					<answer value="d">The peer reviewers.</answer>					<answer value="e">None of the above.</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>When does the public usually find out via the media about new findings that may have an impact on public-health issues?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">When the paper is submitted to a journal.</answer>					<answer value="b">At a press conference announcing the results of research.</answer>					<answer value="c">After the article has been accepted by a journal.</answer>					<answer value="d">After the article has been published by a journal.</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>Which of the following is not an accepted practice for a peer reviewer?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">Making critical comments about the quality of research.</answer>					<answer value="b">Using ideas in the paper or grant application to stop personal research that appears unfruitful.</answer>					<answer value="c">Using ideas in the paper or grant application to advance personal research.</answer>					<answer value="d">Sharing information in a paper or grant application with others.</answer>					<answer value="e">All of the above.</answer>					<answer value="f">Two of the above.</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>What are some of the ways that researchers are considering to improve the process of peer review of publications?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">Having both authors and reviewers know who is reviewing the paper.</answer>					<answer value="b">Having both authors and reviewers not know the identity of one another during the review process.</answer>					<answer value="c">Posting submitted articles on the Internet to obtain review from a larger community of peers before publication.</answer>					<answer value="d">All of the above.</answer>					<answer value="e">Two of the above.</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>			<question type="single-choice">							<text>Which of the following are possible conflicts of interest for a peer reviewer?</text>							<answers>									<answer value="a">Owning stock in a company that is doing research similar to the submitted paper's.</answer>					<answer value="b">Having a religious idea that may conflict with the topic of the paper.</answer>					<answer value="c">Researching the same topic as the submitted paper's.</answer>					<answer value="d">Disliking the author of the paper.</answer>					<answer value="e">All of the above.</answer>					<answer value="f">Three of the above.</answer>								</answers>							<explanation>TBA</explanation>						</question>	</module></quiz>